SWEENEY ARNETT

WEB DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Meticulous problem solver who works well in teams and looks forward to new challenges. Proven experience succeeding under tight deadlines and adapting to change. Focused on achieving a balance between utility and design through clean and concise code.

CONTACT

sweeneyarnett.com

♀ Seattle, WA

in /sweeneyarnett/

sweeneyyy

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: HTML, CSS, Javascript, SQL, Python **FRAMEWORKS:** Bootstrap,

Express, NodeJS, ReactJS, Django

DATABASES: PostgreSQL,

Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose **OTHER:** AJAX, Git, Github, Heroku

EDUCATION

General Assembly

Web Development Immersive 2018

University of North Florida

Bachelor of Business
Administration, Finance 2009

PROJECTS

Whereabouts

A vision board app that allows a user to search images from tumblr by their tag. Built with Node, js, Express, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Javascript, HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.

Venture!

A full-stack MERN app built in collaboration with Tony Phan and Winston Summers at General Assembly. A user can create an account to search their next travel destination and save popular restaurants via the Yelp API along with creating a packing list.

EMPLOYMENT

Keller Williams Realty

Realtor/Team Manager

Boca Raton, FL Sep 2012 to Nov 2017

- Managed daily operations of a top performing team and provided a high level of customer service to all clients.
- Created and improved systems for goal tracking, listing and transaction coordination, marketing and lead generation.
- Responsible for the contract to closing process and reviewed contracts, monitored all deadlines and coordinated with all parties

Knowledge Universe

Human Resources Specialist

Portland, OR Jun 2011 to Aug 2012

- Supportive member of the benefits team responding to employee inquiries and providing accurate information, according to law and policy.
- Processed requests to add, change or cancel insurance coverage and reviewed applicant paperwork to ensure compliance with company policy.
- Initiated and reviewed national criminal background checks using ADP.

Keller Williams Realty

Portland, OR

Executive Assistant

Mar 2010 to Mar 2011

- Supported lead agent in daily operations of the team to allow them to focus on growing the business.
- Proactively sought ways to improve team marketing and branding and monitored and maintained all paperwork and transaction coordination.
- Updated and maintained team contact database, website and calendar. Prepared market reports evaluating inventory and sales volume.

VOLUNTEERING

KW Cares, Keller Williams Realty Boca Raton, FL

2012 to 2017

BodyVox Dance Co. · Individual Giving Committee Portland, OR

Feb 2010 to Jun 2010